Western Federation of Miners International Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Records 5268
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Interviews, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Notes taken during Professor Jensen's interviews with the following individuals. Embree, Sam. Chicago, Illinois, July 13, 1948. Graham, James P., Helena, Montana, August 7, 1946. Hawkins, Horace Sr. Denver, Colorado, September 10, 1946. Park, Charoes. New York, New York, June 23, 1949. Robinson, Reid. Chicago, Illinois, June 27, 1950.
- Newspapers and Periodicals (Notes), Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Notes, mostly handwritten, from various sources.
- Butte, Montana Newspapers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Handwritten notes from Butte Montana newspapers
- Books, Pamphlets, etcetera (Notes), Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Engineering and Mining Journal (Correspondence), 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Includes research notes.
- Engineering and Mining Journal, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Handwritten notes from the Journal.
- Government Publications - Fifty-Sixth (56th) Congress, 1899-1900 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  From Senate Documents vols. 4 and 9.
  - Item 1: Report of Brigadier General H. C. Merriam, USA, On Miners' Riots in the State of Idaho, 1899; Text (Box 4, Folder 8)
    From Senate Documents v.4:no.24, "Coeur d'Alene Mining Troubles". Pp. 1-15
    Format: Text.
  - Item 2: Report of Brigadier General H. C. Merriam, USA, On Miners' Riots in the State of Idaho, 1899; Text (Box 4, Folder 8)
    From Senate Documents v.4:no.24, "Coeur d'Alene Mining Troubles". Pp. 16-25
  - Item 3: Letter from the Secretary of War, 1900; Text (Box 4, Folder 8)
    From Senate Documents v.9:no.142, "Coeur d'Alene Mining Troubles". 15 pages.
- Miners Magazine, 1901-1912 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Handwritten notes from the magazine.
- Government Publications - Sixty-Fourth (64th) Congress, 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Documents from Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4, and Documents from Senate Documents v.27, Commission on Industrial Relations Final Report and Testimony v.9. Includes handwritten notes
  - Item 1: Testimony of Thomas J. Grier, Joseph F. Busch, D. C. Warren, and James Kirwan, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4: Grier, pages 3542-3587; Busch, pages 3588-3599; Warren, page 3600; Kirwan, pages 3602-3606.
  - Item 2: Continuation of Testimony of James Kirwan, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4. Kirwan, pages 3603-3607; Irwin, pages 3608-3613; Clough, pages 3614-3615; Ryan, pages 3619-3620; Scoggan, pages 3621-3624; Northam, pages 3632-3634; Smith, pages 3643-3646; Grier (recalled), pages 3647-3649; Grier Exhibit, pages 3664-3667.
  - Item 3: Testimony of C. F. Kelley and Clarence A. Smith, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4: Kelley, pages 3683-3719; Smith, pages 3723-3727.
  - Item 4: Testimony of Clarence A. Smith, Dennis Murphy, Dan Sullivan, Dan Shovlin, W. L. O'Brien, and Jacob Oliver, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4: Smith, pages 3727-3734; Murphy, pages 3737-3740; Sullivan, pages 3761-3771; Shovlin, pages 3772-3777; O'Brien, pages 3778-3779; Oliver, pages 3780-3785.
  - Item 5: Testimony of Jacob Oliver, J. B. Rankin, E. P. Mathewson, William B. Daly, Lownes Maury, Joe Shannon, and C. F. Kelley, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4: Oliver, pages 3785; Rankin; Mathewson, pages 3795; Daly, pages 3796-3797; Maury, pages 3801-3807; Shannon, pages 3852-3859; Kelley (revised), pages 3860-3882.
  - Item 6: Report of Conditions Noted in Streets, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.22, Commission on Industrial Relations Report and Testimony v.4, pages 3882-3910. M. J. McNallan, MD. Includes Kelly Exhibits 8, 11, and 12. 8 pages
  - Item 7: Activities of Miami Copper Co. with Respect to the Social and Industrial Welfare of its Employees, Text (Box 4, Folder 10)
    From Senate Documents v.27, Commission on Industrial Relations Final Report and Testimony v.9, pages 8359-8361.
- Government Publication - Miscellaneous, Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Notes from Government publications
  - Item 1: Report from the Industrial Commission, 1901; Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes from vols. 5, 6, and 7
  - Item 2: Notes from Labor Disturbances in Colorado, Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Pages 47-50
  - Item 3: Notes from Labor Disturbances in Colorado, Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Pages 51-67
  - Item 4: Notes from Labor Disturbances in Colorado, Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Pages 132-146
  - Item 5: Notes from A Short History of the War Manpower Commission, 1948; Text (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Pages 86- 102
- Proceedings - Notes, Text (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Notes from International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers and Western Federation of Miners conventions.
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers - Miscellaneous Notes, Text (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Non-Ferrous Metals Industry - Miscellaneous Notes, Text (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Western Federation of Miners - Miscellaneous Notes, Text (Box 4, Folder 15)
- McLenegan - Early Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Five letters written as Secretary of Butte Miners (Local Ho. l), one letter written as chairman of "Miner's Organization Committee. " 6 pieces
- Butte Mineworkers Independent Union, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  September 1922-March 1923. Papers relating to the creation of an independent union of mine-workers in the Silver Bow region of Montana, September, 1922 to March 1923. 12 pieces
- McLenegan to Brown, Thomas H. - Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Letters and telegrams written as a member of the Executive Beard and as organizer in the field to the President of the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers. 53 pieces.
- Thomas H. Brown to McLenegan - Correspondence, 1934; Text (Box 4, Folder 19)
- McLenegan to Robinson, James - Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Letters and telegrams written to the Secretary-Treasurer of the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, December, 1933, to January, 1935, concerning union affairs, organizing campaigns, the strike at the Liberty Montana Mines (May- August, 1934), financial matters, and personalities. McLenegan and Robinson seem to have been old friends; the latter's son Reid was financial secretary of Butte Miners No. 1 until his election to the presidency of the International in October of 1934 and several letters mention his activities. 120 pieces
- James Robinson to McLenegan - Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Letters and telegrams written by the Secretary-Treasurer of tube International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers. Robinson remained at the International's offices In Salt lake City during most of this period. 71 pieces.
- Executive Board - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1937 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Letters and telegrams to or from IUMMSW officers George R. Coles, Vice-president; Charles J. Whitely, Daniel Orlich, Thomas S. Cole, members of the Executive Board, and President Reid Robinson. 32 pieces
- Organization and Internal Affairs of Several Locals, Text (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Papers relating to the several locals of the IUMMSW, and the attempts of workers or International Officials to organize additional local unions; Butte Miners No. 1; Great Falls M & S No. 16; Twin Bridges M & M Ho. 19; Pony M & M No. 21 (absorbed Mammoth Miners as part of agreement between Mammoth Miners and Liberty Montana Mine Co., 23 August 1934); Bennack M & M No. 22; Basin Miners No. 23; Phillipsburg M & M Ho. 24' Tooele (Utah) M & S No. 55; Butte Stationary Engineers No. 83; Anaconda M & S No. 117; Logan (Montana) cement workers; Helena; Virginia City (Montana); Deer Lodge; Big Timber; Fort Peck (U. S. Government project under direction of Army Engineers); Jardine. Considerable other information will be found in the correspondence cited above.
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers Executive Papers, 1926-1934 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Accountant's report, 9 July 1931; Secretary- Treasurer's Reports; April 1926, May 1928, June-August 1931, April- June and September-November 1933; Minutes of the Executive Board: 3 April 1933 and 19 November 1933 to 7 January 1934, the last group concerning especially a dispute as to the legality of the returns filed by Butte Miners Ho. 1, and including papers relating to this election; proposed amendments to the IUMMSW constitution; IUMMSW "reports" to the several locals on union affairs.
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers - Political Activities, Text (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Papers relating to the attempts of the International to influence the course of National legislation or local elections, See also correspondence to and from Brown concerning the copper code under NIRA. 10 pieces
- McLenegan - Miscellaneous Papers, Text (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Unidentifiable or otherwise miscellaneous papers, including IUMMSW printed material (contract forms, price lists, charters, blank ballots, & c.), receipts, some correspondence, lists of names, minutes of meetings, material on scabs, comments on the advantages of a six-hour day (e.g.), and some material relating to the organization of a farmer-labor cooperative and a Montana State Mining Council. Other papers on these last subjects will be found scattered through McLenegan's correspondence, especially to James Robinson.
- Periodical and Other Printed Material, 1933-1938 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Newspapers and handbills.
  - Item 1: (Butte) Miners and Engineers Election of Officers I. U. of M. M. and S. W., 1933; Broadsides (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Handbill. 4 October 1933
    Format: Broadsides.
  - Item 2: Mass Meeting of Tunnel Workers ... May 5, 1934 ..Indian, Calif.... Called by J. C. Whitely, Broadsides (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Handbill
  - Item 3: No More Layoffs! Keep the Mines Operating! Work Belief at Once - At A. C. M. EXPENSE!, 1937; Broadsides (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Handbill. November 1937: issued by Communist Party of Montana, Butte
  - Item 4: Montana Labor News, 1926; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1926:Apr. 22)
  - Item 5: Montana Labor News, 1934; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.9:no.46 (1934:Jan. 18)
  - Item 6: Miner's Voice, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Author: Butte Miners local No. 1
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1935:Jan.)
  - Item 7: Miner's Voice, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1935:Feb.)
  - Item 8: Miner's Voice, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1935:Mar.)
  - Item 9: Miner's Voice, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1935:Mar.) Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Miner's Voice, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1935:Apr.)
  - Item 11: Miner's Voice, 1936; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1936:Mar.)
  - Item 12: Miner's Voice, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1938)
  - Item 13: Miner's Voice, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1938:Nov.)
  - Item 14: Miner's Voice, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1937:Feb.)
  - Item 15: A.F. of L. Rank and File Federationist, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Author: Trade Union Committee for Unemployment Insurance and Relief
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1935:Feb.)
  - Item 16: A.F. of L. Rank and File Federationist, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1935:Mar./Apr.)
- Bulletin (One Issue), 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Industrial Workers of the World (IWW)
    Notes: no.1 (1922:Oct. 18)
- The Butte Bulletin (Daily), 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  May 16-June 1, 1921
  - Item 1: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Author: Bulletin Publishing Co.
    Notes: v.3:no.230 (1921:May 16)
  - Item 2: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.238 (1921:May 25)
  - Item 3: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.239 (1921:May 26)
  - Item 4: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.240 (1921:May 27)
  - Item 5: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.241 (1921:May 28)
  - Item 6: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.243 (1921:May 31)
  - Item 7: The Butte Daily Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.3:no.244 (1921:June 1)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  September 2-October 21, 1921
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.246 (1921:June 17)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.247 (1921:June 24)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.249 (1921:July 8)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.250 (1921:July 15)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.251 (1921:July 22)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.252 (1921:July 29)
  - Item 7: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.253 (1921:Aug. 5)
  - Item 8: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.254 (1921:Aug. 12)
  - Item 9: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.255 (1921:Aug. 19)
  - Item 10: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.256 (1921:Aug. 26)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  October 28-December 2, 1921
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.257 (1921:Sept. 2)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.258 (1921:Sept. 9)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.259 (1921:Sept. 16)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.260 (1921:Sept. 23)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.261 (1921:Sept. 30)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.262 (1921:Oct. 7)
  - Item 7: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.3:no.264 (1921:Oct. 21)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  July 15-August 26, 1921
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.3:no.265 (1921:Oct. 28)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1921:Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1921:Nov. 11)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1921:Nov. 18)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1921:Nov. 25)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1921:Dec. 2)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1921-1922 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  December 9, 1921-January 13, 1922.
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1921:Dec. 9)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1921:Dec. 16)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1921:Dec. 23)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1921:Dec. 30)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1922:Jan. 6)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.4:no.11 (1922:Jan. 13)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  January 20-February 24, 1922
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.12 (1922:Jan. 20)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.13 (1922:Jan. 27)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.14 (1922:Feb. 3)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.15 (1922:Feb. 10)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.16 (1922:Feb. 17)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.4:no.17 (1922:Feb. 24)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  March 3-August 4, 1922
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.18 (1922:Mar. 3)
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.20 (1922:Mar. 17)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.21 (1922:Mar. 24)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.22 (1922:Mar. 31)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.23 (1922:Apr. 7)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.4:no.25 (1922:Aug. 4)
- The Butte Bulletin, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  August 11, 1922-February 16, 1923
  - Item 1: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.4:no.26 (1922:Aug. 11). Printed as v.5:no.26.
  - Item 2: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1922:Aug. 25)
  - Item 3: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1922:Sept. 1)
  - Item 4: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1922:Sept. 8)
  - Item 5: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1922:Sept. 15)
  - Item 6: The Butte Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1922:Oct. 13)
  - Item 7: The Butte Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.5:no.26 (1923:Feb. 16)
- The Butte Daily Post (One Issue), 1917; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Butte Daily Post, 1917; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Author: Butte Daily Post Publishing Co.
    Notes: v.5:no.183 (1917:Aug. 1)
- California Branch, General Defense Committee Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Author: California Branch of the General Defense Committee
    Notes: September 22, 1923.
- Defense News Bulletin (Four Issues), 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Defense News Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Author: General Defense Committee, IWW.
    Notes: January 10, 1918.
  - Item 2: Defense News Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.13 (1918:Feb. 9)
  - Item 3: Defense News Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.14 (1918:Feb. 16)
  - Item 4: Defense News Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.25 (1918:May 4)
- Free Society (One Issue), 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Free Society, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Author: Anarchist Groups of United States and Canada
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1921:May)
- General Construction Workers Bulletin (One Issue), 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: General Construction Workers Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Author: General Construction Workers Industrial Union No. 310
    Notes: no.8 (1923:Nov. 10)
- General Office Bulletin (Two Issues), 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: General Office Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Notes: July, 1923.
  - Item 2: General Office Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Notes: November, 1923.
- Good Morning (One Issue), 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Good Morning, 1921; Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Author: Good Morning Co.
    Notes: v.3:no.8 (1921:May 1- 15)
- The Industrial Pioneer (Two Issues), 1923-1925 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  1923 and 1925
  - Item 1: The Industrial Pioneer, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Author: General Executive Board of the IWW
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1923:Nov.)
  - Item 2: The Industrial Pioneer, 1925; Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1925:June)
- Industrial Solidarity (Three Issues), 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Industrial Solidarity, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Notes: no.231 (1923:Apr. 7)
  - Item 2: Industrial Solidarity, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Notes: no.239 (1923:June 2)
  - Item 3: Industrial Solidarity, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Notes: no.344 (1923:July 7)
- The Industrial Worker (Six Issues), 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Author: Organ of the Western Branches, IWW
    Notes: v.5:no.27 (whole no.235) (1923:June 9)
  - Item 2: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: v.5:no.29 (whole no.237) (1923:June 16)
  - Item 3: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: v.5:no.30 (whole no.238) (1923:June 20)
  - Item 4: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: v.5:no.34 (whole no.242) (1923:July 4)
  - Item 5: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: v.5:no.38 (whole no.246) (1923:July 18)
  - Item 6: The Industrial Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: v.5:no.39 (whole no.247) (1923:July 21)
- Lumber Workers Bulletin (One Issue), 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Lumber Workers' Bulletin, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Author: Lumber Workers' Industrial Union No. 120, IWW
    Notes: no.11 (1923:Jan. 1)
- Metal Miners' Bulletin (Two Issues), 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Metal Miners' Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Author: Metal Mine Workers Industrial Union No. 800, IWW
    Notes: September 9, 1918.
  - Item 2: Metal Miners' Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Notes: September 20, 1918.
- Miscellaneous News Clippings, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
- The Red Labor Union International Bulletin, 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Red Labor Union International Bulletin of the Executive Bureau, 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Red Trade Union International
    Notes: no.1 (1921:Aug. 30)
- American Civil Liberties Union, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Fight for Civil Liberty: The Story of the Activities of the American Civil Liberties Union 1928-29, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: American Civil Liberties Union
    Notes: June 1929. 47 pp.
  - Item 2: The Fight for Civil Liberty, 1927-28: The Story of the Year 1927- of the Courts, Laws, Police, Schools, Public Opinion - With Prospectus Ahead, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: 71 pp.
  - Item 3: Free Speech 1925-26: The Work of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: April, 1926. 47 pp.
  - Item 4: The Truth About the I.W.W. Prisoners, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: April, 1922. 47 pp.